elitemysteryshopper.com 2015-02-12

# Elite Mystery Shopper

**EliteMysteryShopper.com  
PRIVACY POLICY  
Effective Date: August 2, 2010  
Last Updated: December 27, 2010**

**Our Commitment To Privacy and Restrictions on Use of Our Site**  
EliteMysteryShopper.com ("Site") is an Internet property of WebWorks, a division of Site Central, LLC ("we," "us"). Your privacy is important to us. In this statement we explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. We will use reasonable efforts to make this statement available via a link on our homepage and elsewhere on our site for easy reference. 

Our Site may not be used by persons under eighteen (18) years of age, or persons who are not residents of the United States. Persons in these categories must not disclose any information to us, or use this Site. We do not knowingly request, solicit or collect information from persons under eighteen (18) years of age, or from anyone who is not a United States resident. We define "United States" as the fifty (50) states, plus U.S. territories, including the Midway Islands, Puerto Rico, American Samoa, Virgin Islands, Micronesia, Marshall Islands, Northern Mariana Islands, Palau and Guam. 

We contract with data providers and payment processors (collectively "Service Providers") to deliver the data in our Members’ Area, and process payments from Members. If you make a purchase, you will be providing your information to our Service Providers. We may also obtain certain information from you, and we may contact you directly without using our Service Providers. Any information you provide may be shared between us and our Service Providers.  We are not responsible for our Service Providers' privacy policies and recommend you read their privacy policies carefully.  If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or our Service Providers' privacy policies, contact us for assistance.

We may use your email address to notify you of program updates, and we may send you certain transactional messages relating to the EliteMysteryShopper.com service, such as service announcements, administrative messages, and similar messages that are considered part of your EliteMysteryShopper.com account.   We may sell or transfer this information if we sell our business or its assets.

**How We Collect and Use Information:   Cookies, Clear gifs, and Other Means**  
Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive which help us recognize you as a user or Member and assist you in navigating the Site as easily as possible.  We use cookies to recognize users and collect information about how our Site is used. Information gathered from cookies may include the date and time of visits, the Site pages viewed, time spent at our Site and the websites that you visited just before and just after your visit to our Site. If you do not wish to transmit "cookie" information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser. Please consult the "Help" section of your web browser in order to correctly turn off or disable the cookie functions. However, turning off or disabling the cookie functions on your web browser may prevent our system from recognizing you when you visit our Site, and consequently may make utilization of the Site more difficult, or even impossible.

We may also use "clear gifs" (which also have other names, such as "pixel tags") and/or JavaScript plug-ins, on our website and in our emails to you. These are small graphic images or code which are used for such things as recording web pages and links clicked-on by a user, or for tracking the performance of email marketing campaigns. These devices help us measure the effectiveness of our Site and our marketing. We may work with third-party service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information.  Third-party entities with whom we have agreements may also place these devices on the Site and/or in emails to use information obtained from them such as pages viewed, items purchased, emails opened and items upon which you may click in emails.

A "widget" is generally an application that can be embedded in a web page.  Widgets can provide real-time information to the page.  Widgets are often provided by third-parties and we may provide widgets on our Site.  Widgets may enable the third-parties that provide them to collect data about users visiting this Site.  Also by clicking on certain widgets, some of your information may be shared with the third-party placing the widget.  We may also obtain information shared with us through the providers of these widgets. 

Our Site's servers also automatically identify your computer by its IP address, which is a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider. IP addresses are automatically logged by web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Internet. Your IP address can also reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Your IP address may be used to address problems with our server, administer our Site and/or to gather broad demographic information about our users and Members. Finally, the other websites that you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages.

We reserve the right to employ user and Member source information, including applicable category and interest(s), for marketing purposes. This source information may be shared with our third party marketing partners. We also reserve the right to retain cookie, pixel tag and widget data indefinitely.  We may sell or transfer this information if we sell or transfer our business.

Finally, we will comply with legal, judicial or administrative authorities in the event that information must be reviewed or released in response to civil and/or criminal investigations, claims, lawsuits, or if we are subject to judicial or administrative process (such as a subpoena) to release your information or to prosecute or defend legal actions. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**  
We collect various types of personal information about you during the course of your relationship with us as a user or Member. Under California law, if you are a resident of California, you may make a written request to us about how we have shared your information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To exercise your rights under California law, please send your written request to the email address or postal address given below. Please include your postal address in your request.

**Visitors to the Website Outside of the United States**  
If you are visiting the Site from a location outside of the U.S., your connection will be through and to servers located in the U.S.  The data protection laws in the U.S. might not be as those in your country.  By using this Site and/or submitting information to us, you specifically consent to the transfer of your information to the U.S. and to the facilities and servers we use, within or outside the U.S., and to those with whom we may share your information.

**Unsubscribe/Opt-Out**  
To unsubscribe or opt-out of receiving future commercial communications from us, or from our affiliates, please [Click Here](http://webworks.webwks.com/5509e0ed3bd1fa999ba41ed3564adc64) and enter your email address in our unsubscribe system. Please note, however, that when you select this option, we may still send you emails and other communications regarding any transactions that you entered into by and through the Site while you were a Member. 

**Changes**  
We may elect to change or amend our privacy policy; in such event, we will post the policy changes in our privacy policy on the Site. If you are concerned about how your personal information is used, please visit our Site often for this and other important announcements and updates.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or need help with anything related to our Privacy Policy, you may [email us](mailto:support@EliteMysteryShopper.com) or send a written request to our Customer Service Manager at the following address: 

Customer Service Manager  
EliteMysteryShopper.com  
c/o WebWorks   
7 East 8th Street   
Suite 362   
New York, NY 10003
